Guide to the Richard W. Lyman, Provost of Stanford University, Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Papers, 1959-1972
  - Engineering, School of, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Engineering-Applied Mathematics, Undated (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Engineering-Aeronautics and Astronautics, Undated (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Engineering-Bioengineering, Undated (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Electrical Engineering, Undated (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Engineering-Economic Systems, Undated (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Hansen Laboratories, Undated (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Industrial Engineering, Undated (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Materials Research, Center for, Undated (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Engineering Institute for Plasma Research, Undated (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Department of Materials Science, Undated (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Mechanical Engineering, Undated (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Engineering Operations Research, Undated (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Humanities and Sciences, Undated (Box 13, Folder 28)
    - Anthropolgy, Undated (Box 13, Folder 29)
    - Art and Architecture, Undated (Box 13, Folder 30)
    - Sociology/Anthropology Special File (RWL's file), Undated (Box 13, Folder 31)
    - Applied Physics, Undated (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Asian Languages, Undated (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Biological Sciences, Undated (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Chemistry, Undated (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Classics, Undated (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Committee on Linguistics (file empty), Undated (Box 13, Folder 37)
    - Communication, Undated (Box 13, Folder 38)
    - Computer Science, Undated (Box 13, Folder 39)
    - Economics, Undated (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - English, Undated (Box 14, Folder 41)
    - French and Italian, Undated (Box 14, Folder 42)
    - History, Undated (Box 14, Folder 43)
    - History: Afro-American, Undated (Box 14, Folder 44)
    - Hopkins Marine Station, Undated (Box 14, Folder 45)
    - Mathematics, Undated (Box 14, Folder 46)
    - Military Science, Undated (Box 14, Folder 47)
    - Modern European Languages, Undated (Box 14, Folder 48)
    - Music, Undated (Box 14, Folder 49)
    - Physics, Undated (Box 14, Folder 50)
    - Philosophy, Undated (Box 14, Folder 51)
    - Political Science, Undated (Box 14, Folder 52)
    - Psychology, Undated (Box 14, Folder 53)
    - Slavic Department, Undated (Box 14, Folder 54)
    - Sociology, Undated (Box 14, Folder 55)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, Undated (Box 14, Folder 56)
    - Speech and Drama, Undated (Box 14, Folder 57)
    - Special Programs in Humanities, Undated (Box 14, Folder 58)
    - Statistics Department, Undated (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - School of Law, Undated (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Medical School Mater Plan, Undated (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - School of Medicine, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - School of Medicine, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - School of Medicine, 1967-1968 (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Other Departments, Institutes, and Programs
    - Aphasia Institute, Undated (Box 14, Folder 65)
    - Athletics--Pacific 8 Conference, Undated (Box 14, Folder 66)
    - Biophysics Laboratory, Undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Communication Research, Institute for, Undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Nursing Program, Department of, Undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Physical Education-Women, Undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - ROTC Disruptions, R.W. Lyman, 1970 April (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - ROTC, R.M. Rosenzweig, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - -C- ROTC, 1969-1970 (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - -C- ROTC, R.W.L., 1967-1968 (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - ROTC, Army. President Files. R.M.R., Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - ROTC, Navy. President's Office Files. R.M.R., Undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Leaves
    - -P- Misc., Undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - -P- School of Business, Graduate, Undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Leaves-Earth Sciences, Undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - -P- School of Education, Undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - -P- School of Engineering, Undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - -P- Food Research Institute, Undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Humanities and Sciences, Undated (Box 15, Folder 16A)
    - -P- School of Medicine, Undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - -P- School of Law, Undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - -P- Physical Education for Women, Undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Visiting Committees
    - Committees: General, Undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Committee Roster, Undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - A.A.U.P. Commission (file empty), Undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Te Vega, Advisory Committee, Undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Computer Science, Advisory Committee on (Visiting), Undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Earth Science, Advisory Committee on, Undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
    - School of Education, Visiting Committee, Undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
    - The Hoover Institution, Advisory Board of, Undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
    - School of Medicine, Visiting Committee, Undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Advisory Board, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Advisory Board, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Advisory Board: Forms, Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Academic Council, 1969-1971 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Executive Committee (Academic Council), Undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Senate (Academic Council) Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Senate (Academic Council) Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Senate (Academic Council) Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Absences, Unexcused, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Affirmative Action Program, Undated (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Affirmative Action Committee, Undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - African and Afro-American Studies, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Alumni Conferences, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Architecture, Special Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Athletics and Physical Education, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - The University Budget Adjustment Program, Advisory Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Buildings and Grounds, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Campus Planning, Committee on (Board of Trustees) (file empty), Undated (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Clubhouse Advisory Board (file empty), Undated (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Committee on Committees. Correspondence, Undated (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Committee on Committees, Charges to, Undated (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Computer, Advisory (Internal) Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - University Policy (COUP), Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Draft Deferments (ad hoc), Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - East Asian Library, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Economics, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Employment Grievance, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Enrollment Policies, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Facilities Group, Undated (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Faculty Benefits, Committee on (AAUP), Undated (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Faculty Consultative Group, Undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Faculty Handbook, Presidential Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Faculty Hearings Group Interim Panel, Undated (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Faculty Information, Committee on (ad hoc), Undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Faculty and Staff Affairs, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Fallout Shelter, Civil Defence, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Fifteen, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Financial Awards, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Foreign Languages, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Foreign Students, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Foreign Study Programs, Committee on, Undated (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - General Studies, Committee on, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Government Policy, Committee on (RWL), Undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Governmental Policy toward Universities, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Haas Sloan Lectures Committee, Undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Housing Needs, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Human Biology, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Human Subjects, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Humanities and Sciences Faculty Council, 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Humanities and Sciences Faculty Council, 1967-1968 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Innovation Fund, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Interdisciplinary Research, Committee on - Ad Hoc, Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - International Studies, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Land and Building Development, Committee on, 1967-1969 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Library Coordination and Cooperation, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Library Council, Undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Low-Income Housing, Ad Hoc Comm. Correspondence, RWL's file, Undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Low-Income Housing, Committee on (Moulton Committee, etc.), Undated (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Low-Income Housing, Ad Hoc Comm., 1969-1970 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Medical and Engineering Biosciences, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Medicine, School of. Administrative Committee, Undated (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Memberships and Privileges, Committee on (Senate Ad Hoc), Undated (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - W.F. Miller's Advisory Group, Undated (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Minority Affairs, Comm. On, Undated (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Minority Employment, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - New Undergraduate Living Ideas, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Overseas Campuses, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Palo Alto Clinic - S.U. Liaison, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Parking and Traffic Committee, Undated (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Planning Coordinating, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Planning and Development, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Presidential Committees, Undated (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Privacy of Information, Committee on (ad hoc), Undated (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Public Exercises, Events, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Research Policy, Committee on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Residential Education, Study Group on, Undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Residential Education, Undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Student Participation in Political Processes, Committee on, Undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Research Subcommittee, Computer Advisory Comm. (Int.), Undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Room and Board Rates, Committee on, Undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Selective Service, Committee on, Undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Services to Students, (Coss) Committee on, Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - SLAC Coordinating Committee, Undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - SLAC Scientific Policy Committee, Undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Stanford Today and Tomorrow Executive Committee, Undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Student Development, Committee on, Undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Student-Faculty Employment, Committee on, Undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Student Financial Aid, Committee on, Undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - S.U. Violence, Commission on, Undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Task Force for Special Minority Students Program, Undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Teaching Assistantship, Committee on, Undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Transfer-Cooperative Program (Task Force), Undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Two, Committee of, Undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Undergraduate Admission, Committee on, Undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Undergraduate Studies, Committee on, Undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - University Advisory Committee, Undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - University Operations Review, Undated (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - University Security, Committee on, Undated (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Urban Public Economics, Committee on, Undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Women's Forum Steering Committee, Undated (Box 18, Folder 24)